const VocabularyQuestion=[
    {
        question: "What do you call the bright, shining object that lights up the sky during the day?",
        options: ["Moon", "Star ", "Sun", "Dark"],
        correct_option: "Sun"
      },
      {
        question: "What do you call the season with cold weather, snow, and sometimes ice?",
        options: ["summer", "Winter ", "Spring", "Fall"],
        correct_option: "Winter"
      },
      {
        question: "hich word means the opposite of happy?",
        options: ["Sad", "Funny ", "Excited", "Tired"],
        correct_option: "Sad"
      },
      {
        question: "What is the name for a building where you live?",
        options: ["School", " Hospital", "House", "Library"],
        correct_option: "House"
      },
      {
        question: "What is the opposite of day?",
        options: ["Morning", " Night", "Evening", "Afternoon"],
        correct_option: "Night"
      },
      {
        question: "What color is a lemon?",
        options: ["Red", " Blue", "Yellow", "Green"],
        correct_option: "Yellow"
      },
      {
        question: "What color is the sky on a sunny day?",
        options: ["Yellow", " Blue", "Orange", "Green"],
        correct_option: "Blue"
      },
      {
        question: "What animal says meow and is often kept as a pet?",
        options: ["Cat", " Rabit", "Horse", "Dog"],
        correct_option: "Cat"
      },
      {
        question: "What animal has a long trunk and big ears?",
        options: ["Lion", "Zebra ", "Monkey", "Elephant "],
        correct_option: "Zebra"
      },
      {
        question: "What fruit is round, red, and often used to make apple pie?",
        options: ["Banana", "Apple ", "Strawberry", "Orange"],
        correct_option: "Apple"
      },
      {
        question: "What vegetable is green, crunchy, and often used in salads?",
        options: ["Carrot", "Broccoli ", "Potato", "Cucumber"],
        correct_option: "Broccoli"
      },

];
export default VocabularyQuestion;